Enough Said is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Nicole Holofcener.
Eva is a divorced soon-to-be empty-nester wondering about her next act.
Then she meets Marianne, the embodiment of her perfect self.
Armed with a restored outlook on being middle-aged and single, Eva decides to take a
chance on her new love interest Albert — a sweet, funny and like-minded man.
But things get complicated when Eva discovers that Albert is
in fact the dreaded ex–husband of Marianne...
Eva, played by Julia Louis-Dreyfus.
Albert, played by James Gandolfini.
Marianne, played by Catherine Keener.
Sarah, played by Toni Collette.
Chloe, played by Tavi Gevinson.
Will, played by Ben Falcone.
Enough Said is a 2013 American romantic comedy-drama film
written and directed by Nicole Holofcener.
The film stars Julia Louis-Dreyfus, James Gandolfini,
Catherine Keener, Toni Collette and Ben Falcone.
Louis-Dreyfus plays Eva, a divorced masseuse who begins a relationship with Albert (Gandolfini), only
to discover that he is the former husband of her client and friend Marianne (Keener).
Holofcener wrote the script, which was partly inspired by her own life, after she was approached by
two producers from Fox Searchlight Pictures who offered to produce her next project.
It was filmed in Los Angeles on a budget of $8 million.
Gandolfini died after the film was completed but before it was
released; Holofcener dedicated the film to him.
Enough Said premiered at the 2013 Toronto International Film Festival and was released on what would have been Gandolfini's 52nd
birthday, September 18, 2013, ranking as the fifth best-reviewed wide release of the year, according to Rotten Tomatoes.
The film was praised for Louis-Dreyfus and Gandolfini's performances, as well as Holofcener's screenplay and received several major award nominations, including for a Golden
Globe for Louis-Dreyfus (her first nomination for a film role), a Screen Actors Guild Award, two Independent Spirit Awards and four Critics' Choice Movie Awards.
The film explores themes of parent child relationship,
affectation, thanksgiving, masseuse, dating.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.